Guide to the Robert Fitch Papers WAG.261
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Subject Files
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Albany, 1993-1998 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Annual Reports (Form LM-2), 1992-1998 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Anthony M. Traini (attorney), 1995 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Arthur A. Coia, 1984-2003 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Arthur A. Coia, 1994-2003 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Arthur A. Coia: Election, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Arthur A. Coia: Hearing, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Arthur A. Coia: Lane Kirkland and North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA), 1993-1997 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Arthur A. Coia: Testimony, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Bob Luskin (attorney), 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Buffalo, Utica and Albany, 1998-2002 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Chicago, 1985-1999 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Chicago, 1992-2002 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Chicago, 1993-2000 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Chicago, 1993-2003 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Chicago, 1997-2002 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Chicago: History, 1982-2003 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Colonial Realty, 1993-1999 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Concrete, 1986-1999 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Connecticut, 1998-2001 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Convention, 1994-2003 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Corruption, 1964-2005 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Francesco Scibella, 1985, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Gary R. Wall, 2002, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): General Executive Board Reports, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Harold M. Ickes, 1969, 1996-2000 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Heritage Foundation Report, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Heritage Loan and Investment Company, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): House Judiciary Committee Report, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): James Messera, 1990-1994 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Local 66, 1994-2002 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Local 79, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Local 79: Richard Ello, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Local 95, 1985-1999 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Mike C. Pagano, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): New Jersey, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): New York: Clippings`, 1992-1999 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): New York State Laborers Political Action Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): New York State Laborers Tri-Fund, 1999-2001 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Pete Dinuzzo, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Phone Numbers, undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Robert D. Luskin, 1996-2000 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Ronald Fino (Local 210), 1996 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Salvatore Lanza, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Sam Fresina (Local 190), 1994-2000 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Steve Manos, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): "The Edge: Organized Crime, Business, and Labor Unions", 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): "The Voice of the Rank and File", 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): United States v. Accardo et al, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): United States v. LIUNA, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Wendy Sloan (attorney): Correspondence, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Las Vegas, Nevada: Organized Crime, 1980-2000 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Living Wage, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC), 1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC): Alphonse D'Arco, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC): Declarations, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC): Frank Faro Lupo, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC): James Messera Surveillance Photographs, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC): Joseph M. Giardina, 1994-1998 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC): Louise Furio, 1992-1999 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC): Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations Act (RICO) Complaint, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC): Richard H. Lovell Declaration, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC): Salvatore Lanza, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC): Thomas Fitzgerald, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC): United States v. MTDC: Al Soussi, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC): United States v. MTDC: Complaint, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC): United States v. MTDC: Final Report of Monitor, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC): United States v. MTDC: Monitor's Reports 1-3, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC): United States v. MTDC: Monitor's Reports 4-6, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC): United States v. MTDC: Motion for Partial Summary Judgment, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Mason Tenders District Council (MTDC): Wiretap Transcripts, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Meany, George, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Meany, George: Dissertation by Theodore Christos Liazos, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Meany, George: Jimmy Carter Presidential Administration, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Meany, George: Joseph S. Fay, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - National Labor Committee (NLC), 1994-1998 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - New Jersey Police Unions, 1999-2004 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - New Labor Forum, undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - New Unity Partnership (NUP): Andrew Stern, 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - New Unity Partnership (NUP): Andrew Stern, 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - New York City: Government Corruption, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - New York City District Council of Carpenters (NYCDC), 1986-2002 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - New York City District Council of Carpenters (NYCDC), 1986-2002 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - New York City District Council of Carpenters (NYCDC): United States v. NYCDC, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - New York City District Council of Carpenters (NYCDC): United States v. NYCDC, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - New York City District Council of Carpenters (NYCDC): United States v. NYCDC: Declarations, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - New York City District Council of Carpenters (NYCDC): United States v. NYCDC: People's Summation, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - New York City District Council of Carpenters (NYCDC): United States v. NYCDC: Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations Act (RICO) Complaint, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - New York State Financial Control Board, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Non Profit Organizations: Corruption, 2001-2003 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Norman, Clarence (New York State Assemblyman), 1999-2005 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Notebooks: Calendars, 1992-1998 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Notecards, undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Notecards, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Notecards, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Organized Crime: Al Sharpton, 1981-2002 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Organized Crime: Bibliography, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Organized Crime: DeCavalcante Family, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Organized Crime: Definitions, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Organized Crime: Fred and Joseph Scalamandre, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Organized Crime: Ground Zero (New York City), 1999-2003 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Organized Crime: History, 2002, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Organized Crime: Jacob Javits Center, 1992-1995 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Organized Crime: Neo Mob, 1988-2005 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Organized Crime: South Florida, 2000-2004 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Outsourcing, 1999-2004 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Parkchester South Condominium (Bronx), 2001-2003 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Parvin-Dohrman Company, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Pension Funds, 1985-2002 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Pension Funds, 1989-1992 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Pension Funds, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Pension Funds, 1997-2003 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Pension Funds, 1999-2002 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Pension Funds: Amalgamated Bank: LongView Fund, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Pension Funds: Article by Crystal Ward, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Pension Funds: Audits, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Pension Funds: Bibliography, 1997-2003 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Pension Funds: Capital Consultants, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Pension Funds: Clippings, 1926-1927 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Pension Funds: Corruption, 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Pension Funds: Crisis, 1999-2004 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Pension Funds: Edward Pauk (attorney), 1997-2002 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Pension Funds: Global Crossing, Ltd, 1998-2002 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Pension Funds: Global Crossing, Ltd, 1998-2002 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Pension Funds: Global Crossing, Ltd, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Pension Funds: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), 2001 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Pension Funds: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Edwin D. Hill Embezzlement Scandal, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Pension Funds: Kenneth F. Boehm Testimony, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Pension Funds: Multiemployer Plans, 1996-2003 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Pension Funds: School Construction Authority, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Pension Funds: Terry McAuliffe, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Pension Funds: United States Department of Labor Pension and Welfare Benefits Administration, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Pension Funds: Value America, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Political Corruption, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Presidential Elections, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Quin Rong Wu (immigrant), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Real Estate: Broward County, Florida, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Restaurant Workers, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Rowman and Littlefield (publishers), 2001 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 1995-1998 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 1996-2002 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 1999-2001 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 2000-2005 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 2000-2005 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Andrew Stern, 1997-2004 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Andrew Stern, 1999-2005 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Annual Reports, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Boston: Strike, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Canada, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Charles Ensley, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Corruption, 1953-2004 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Domestic Care Workers, 2000-2005 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Gus Bevona, 1998-2002 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): History, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Home Healthcare Workers, 1995-2004 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Hubert Alpertz, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Labor Reorganization Debate, 2000-2003 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 32BJ, 1966-2001 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 32BJ, 1977-1998 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 32BJ, 1997-2001 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 32BJ, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 32BJ, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 32BJ, 1998-2001 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 32BJ: Brochures, 2000, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 32BJ: Carlos Guzman, 1991, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 32BJ: Indictments, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 32BJ: Indictments, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 32E, 1966-1969 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 32E: George Scalise, 1940-1952 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 32E: Materials from Wayne State University, 1953-1978 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 32E: Materials from Wayne State University, 1964-1969 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Local 1199, 1999-2004 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Los Angeles, 1995-2001 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Los Angeles, 1999-2001 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Los Angeles: Annual Reports (Form LM-2), 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Los Angeles: Janitors Campaign, 1997-1999 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Los Angeles: Janitors Strike, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Marina City, 1963-1964, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Market Analysis, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Material from Paul Pamias, 1997-1999 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Membership Figures, 1980-2001 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): New Unity Partnership, 2002-2004 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): New Unity Partnership, 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): New York Times Clippings, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Orange County, California: Wages, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Organizing, 2002-2004 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Steve Early Articles, 2002-2004 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU): Workplace Complaint, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Slate, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Social Security, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference (New York, NY), 1997, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Strikes, 1999-2004 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Structure Tone, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Taft, Morris E., 1927-1948 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Trump, Donald, 1986-2000 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Trump, Donald: Washington Post Article, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - ULLICO, Inc, 2001-2003 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - ULLICO, Inc, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - ULLICO, Inc, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - ULLICO, Inc: Pension Funds, 1999-2002 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - ULLICO, Inc: Social Investments, 2000-2002 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE), 1956-2005 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE), 1997-2004 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE), 2000-2003 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Annual Reports (Form LM-2), 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Annual Reports (Form LM-2), 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Annual Reports (Form LM-2), 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Benefit Funds, 1999-2002 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Bibliography, 1995-2000 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Clippings, 1996-2008 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Contributions to Political Campaigns, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Correspondence, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Democracy and Structure, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Edgar Romney, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Employee Retirement Income Security Act (ERISA), 1997-2003 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Employment Statistics, undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Request, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Funds, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Health Center, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): International Trade Statistics, 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Jane Latour Manuscript, undated (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Joseph Defede: Indictment, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Local 10, 1995-1998 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Local 23-25: Search Warrant Affidavit, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Mademoiselle Knitwear, 1995-2000 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Mademoiselle Knitwear, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Newsletters, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Organizing, 1998-2004 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Pension Fund, 1998-2002 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Sorrento Coats, 1997-1999 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Sweatshop Leaflet, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Testimony for Committee on Education and the Workforce, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Triangle Shirtwaist Company Fire, 1998, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): Union Corruption Update Articles, 1992-2004 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE): United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW) Membership Raids, 1992-2004 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA), 2001-2006 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): Annual Report (Form 5500), 2001 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): Annual Report (Form LM-2), 2002 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): Diplomat Resort, 1985-2003 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): Diplomat Resort, 1991-2002 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): Diplomat Resort, 2001-2004 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): Diplomat Resort: Arson, 1983-1995 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): Diplomat Resort: Joe Coffey Investigation, 2001-2004 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): Diplomat Resort: Timeline, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): Diplomat Resort: United States Department of Labor v Maddaloni et al, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): Don Sclafani: Charles "Joe" Hynes Fundraiser, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipefitters (UA): Local 1: Indictments, 2000-2003 (Box 15, Folder 20)